{
    "subject": "resource/Barry_Van_Dyke",
    "predicate": "ontology/child",
    "object": "resource/Shane_Van_Dyke",
    "human_readable": "Shane Van Dyke is the child of Barry Van Dyke.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9734169840812683,
            "question": "Is Barry Van Dyke Shane Van Dyke's parent?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9660593271255493,
            "question": "Does Barry Van Dyke have a son named Shane?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8925931453704834,
            "question": "Who are the parents of Shane Van Dyke?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8906627297401428,
            "question": "Is Shane Van Dyke related to Barry Van Dyke?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7619277834892273,
            "question": "Is Barry Van Dyke Shane Van Dyke's biological father?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7479820251464844,
            "question": "To whom is Shane Van Dyke related?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7169414758682251,
            "question": "Who is Shane Van Dyke's father?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7087087035179138,
            "question": "Name Shane Van Dyke's father."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.674891471862793,
            "question": "What is the name of Shane Van Dyke's father?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6091039776802063,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Barry Van Dyke and Shane Van Dyke?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Shane Van Dyke is the child of Barry Van Dyke.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1204_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Shane Van Dyke's father?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1204_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name Shane Van Dyke's father.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1204_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Shane Van Dyke's father?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1204_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1204_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1204_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1204_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1204_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1204_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1204_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1204_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1204_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1204_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1204_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that Barry Van Dyke has four children, and one of them is named Shane Van Dyke. Additionally, other documents provide more information about Shane's career as an actor, writer, and director, further supporting the fact that he is indeed a child of Barry Van Dyke."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Shane Van Dyke is the child of Barry Van Dyke.\" Specifically, multiple sources mention that Shane Van Dyke is Barry Van Dyke's son. For example, from one document: \"Shane Van Dyke (born August 28, 1979) is an American television and film actor, film director, and screenwriter. He is the son of Barry Van Dyke, and grandson of Dick Van Dyke.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}